A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.32 (A2006) FA483
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2006.104: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1997-2004; AC.2006.104; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3817-R3818.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3817-R3818.
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2006.104.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2002 FS 015 - ZAMBIA SEED COMPANY LIMITED - AGRICULTURAL STATISTICAL SOFTWARE DATABASE, 2001-2002 (Box R3817)
    - 2002 FS 018 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - BOOK, "ROCKS FOR CROPS", 2001-2002 (Box R3817)
    - 2002 FS 041 - WEST AFRICA RICE DEVELOPMENT ASSOCIATION (IVORY COAST) - MEETING TO LAUNCH THE AFRICAN RICE INITIATIVE, 2001-2004 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 043 - NORTH CAROLINA STATE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON TRANSGENIC COTTON AND INSECT-RESISTANCE GENES, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 045 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENG' INEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - CONFERENCE ON INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY MANAGEMENT, 2002-2004 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 061 - WAGENINGEN AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (NETHERLANDS) - DEVELOP INTERACTIVE COMPUTER-BASED TEACHING TOOLS FOR BIOLOGICAL NITROGEN FIXATION, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 065 - INSTITUTE OF RURAL ECONOMY (MALI) - NATIONAL WORKSHOP ON AGRICULTURAL BIOTECHNOLOGY, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 081 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIFTH FORUM REGIONAL MEETING, 2001-2002 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 084 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH IN DRY AREAS (SYRIA) - CONFERENCE ON BIOTECHNOLOGY AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 093 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - INTERNATIONAL RICE CONGRESS, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 114 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - FIRST INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON GENOMICS AND CROP GENETIC IMPROVEMENT, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 126 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (COLOMBIA) - CONFERENCE ON SOCIAL SCIENCES AND AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2002-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2002 FS 162 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - DEVELOPMENT OF ITS PROGRAMS (Box R3818)
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.104.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 GI 006 - FOOD AND AGRICULTURE ORGANIZATION OF THE UNITED NATIONS (ITALY) - BIOTECH INFORMATION PAMPHLET FOR AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3818)
    - 2000 GI 015 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - EUROPEAN PARLIAMENTARIANS INITIATIVE, 1997-2003 (Box R3818)
    - 2000 GI 015 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - EUROPEAN PARLIAMENTARIANS INITIATIVE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIALS, 1997-2003 (Box R3818)
- AC.2006.106: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2000-2004; AC.2006.106; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, Box R3819.; 1 standard record storage box, Box R3819.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.106.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 GI 018 - KCTS TELEVISION - ITS DOCUMENTARY HOT POTATOES, 2000-2003 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 045 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - A FRAMEWORK FOR GMOS AND FOOD SECURITY, 2000-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 047 - RURAL ADVANCEMENT FOUNDATION INTERNATIONAL (CANADA) - PARTICIPATION OF RURAL SOCIETIES IN FOOD SECURITY R&D, 2000-2004 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 048 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (CANADA) - IPR IN EARTH NEGOTIATIONS BULLETIN, 2000-2003 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 050 - AMERICAN ACADEMY OF ARTS AND SCIENCES - PUGWASH STUDY GROUP, 1999-2001 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 058 - ROYAL INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS (ENGLAND) - WORKSHOP AND BOOK ON THE "CARTAGENA PROTOCOL ON BIOSAFETY", 2000-2003 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 059 - PARK RIDGE CENTER - ETHICS AND GLOBALIZATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 080 - FINANCIAL MARKETS CENTER - CONFERENCE ON CENTRAL BANKING POLICIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 082 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - RESEARCH AND POLICY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 084 - TIDES CENTER - NSEPC IPR AND NORTH-SOUTH ISSUES, 2000-2003 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 090 - UNITED NATIONS ASSOCIATION OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA - GLOBAL HEALTH AND THE UN SYSTEM, 2000-2001 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 102 - AMERICAN PROSPECT - GLOBALIZAT(ON AND POOR AND MARGINALIZED PEOPLE, 2000-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 105 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - LANDMINE CASE STUDY, 1998-2002 (Box R3819)
    - 2000 GI 107 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR ECONOMIC AND SECURITY ALTERNATIVES - SOCIAL AND ECONOMIC POLICY STRATEGIES AND GLOBALIZATION, 2000-2004 (Box R3819)
- AC.2006.110: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2000-2004; AC.2006.110; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3820-R3821.; 2 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3820-R3821.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.110.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 115 - FIRST NATIONS DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - SECURING INDIGENOUS PEOPLES' HERITAGE, 2000-2001 (Box R3820)
    - 2000 GI 117 - PROJECT HOPE INTERNATIONAL - CHILD PROSTITUTION AND EXPLOITATION IN THAILAND, 2000-2003 (Box R3820)
    - 2000 GI 121 - SOCIAL SCIENTISTS' ASSOCIATION (SRI LANKA) - ARMED CONFLICT AND ETHNIC POLARIZATION, 2000-2003 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 004 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - GLOBAL INTERDEPENDENCE INITIATIVE, 1999-2002 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 009 - PHILANTHROPIC COLLABORATIVE - FUNDERS WORKING GROUP ON BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2004 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 011 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR FOOD AND AGRICULTURAL POLICY - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND PEST MANAGEMENT, 2001-2003 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 014 - NGO COMMITTEE ON DISARMAMENT - UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE ON ILLICIT TRADE OF SMALL ARMS, 2001-2004 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 015 - INTERNATIONAL ALERT (ENGLAND) - 2001 UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE ON SMALL ARMS, 2001-2003 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 016 - U.S. CATHOLIC CONFERENCE - MORAL AND ETHICAL DIMENSIONS OF ECONOMIC GLOBALIZATION, 2001-2002 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 017 - NAUTILUS INSTITUTE FOR SECURITY AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT - VIRTUAL DIASPORAS AND GLOBAL PROBLEM-SOLVING, 2000-2004 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 018 - UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO (CANADA) - INGENUITY THEORY, 2001-2002 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 019 - HUMAN RIGHTS WATCH - COALITION TO STOP THE USE OF CHILD SOLDIERS, 2001-2003 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 020 - TIDES CENTER - BOOK ON PUBLIC POLICY AND GOVERNMENT, 2000-2002 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 021 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - FOURTH INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON THE INFORMATION SOCIETY, 2001-2004 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 023 - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH CENTRE (CANADA) - ICISS AND HUMANITARIAN ACTION, 2000-2002 (Box R3820)
      - Report of the International Commission on Intervention and State Sovereignty, 2006.110.001; 1 Item(s) CD-ROM
    - 2001 GI 024 - INSTITUTE OF GLOBAL ENGAGEMENT - CONFERENCE ON RELIGIOUS GROUPS AND GLOBAL ENGAGEMENT, 2000-2001 (Box R3820)
    - 2001 GI 026 - REGIONAL CENTRE FOR STRATEGIC STUDIES (RCSS) (SRI LANKA) - DIALOGUE BETWEEN SOUTH ASIA AND NON-REGIONAL CENTRES, 1993-2003 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 027 - HUMAN RIGHTS WATCH - PRACTICES OF ARMED NON-STATE GROUPS, 2000-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 031 - INTERNATIONAL LABOUR ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - GLOBALIZATION AND LABOR WITH FOCUS ON WOMEN, 2000-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 033 - INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURE AND TRADE POLICY - MEETING ON AGREEMENT ON TRADE-RELATED ASPECTS OF IPR, 2001-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 034 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - TWO BRIDGES PUBLICATIONS, 2000-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 035 - UNIVERSITY OF VICTORIA (CANADA) - CONFERENCE ON GLOBAL GOVERNANCE, 2001-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 039 - ECONOMIC STRATEGY INSTITUTE - MONOGRAPH ON RECONCILING TRADE AND ENVIRONMENT, 2001-2005 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 043 - PUBLIC CITIZEN FOUNDATION - NORTH AMERICAN FREE TRADE AGREEMENT AND U.S. TRADE POLICYMAKING, 2001-2003 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 044 - PROJECT UNDERGROUND - MINERAL AND ENERGY SECTOR DEVELOPMENT, 2001-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 045 - MONTREAL INTERNATIONAL FORUM (CANADA) - CONFERENCE ON GLOBAL GOVERNANCE, 2001-2004 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 047 - KCTS TELEVISION - TELEVISION PROGRAM ON AG RICULTURAL PRODUCTIVITY AND THE POOR IN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 048 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - APOMIXIS AS A CROP IMPROVEMENT AND ACCESS TO THE TECHNOLOGY (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 049 - NEW ECONOMICS FOUNDATION (ENGLAND) - DEBT RELIEF IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2001-2003 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 052 - INTERNATIONAL LABOR RIGHTS FUND - RIGHTS FOR WORKING WOMEN CAMPAIGN, 2001-2003 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 055 - STIMSON CENTER - SECURITY FOR A NEW CENTURY, 2000-2002 (Box R3821)
    - 2001 GI 056 - WOMEN'S LAW AND PUBLIC POLICY FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM - TRAINING ON WOMEN AND WORK ISSUES, 2001-2003 (Box R3821)
- AC.2006.114: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1992-2005; AC.2006.114; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3822-R3825.; 4 standard record storage boxes, Boxes R3822-R3825.
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2006.114.1; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2001 GI 061 - BLUE MOUNTAIN CENTER - CONFERENCE "LIFE WITH THE GENIE", 2001-2004 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 062 - BRANDEIS UNIVERSITY - YOUTH ACTIVISM AND GLOBAL ENGAGEMENT, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 066 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - ASSESSMENT OF WORLD TRADING SITUATION, 2000-2003 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 069 - CENTER OF CONCERN - GENDER AND TRADE POLICY IN THE AMERICAS, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 071 - WORLD VISION INTERNATIONAL - WORKSHOP ON GENETICALLY MODIFIED ORGANISMS, 2001-2004 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 072 - THIRD WORLD NETWORK (GHANA) - ADVOCACY FOR ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL EQUITY IN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 073 - FIRST NATIONS DEVELOPMENT INSTITUTE - IPR ARRANGEMENTS AND INDIGENOUS PEOPLES, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 075 - WORLD RESOURCES INSTITUTE - BIOSAFETY PROTOCOL, 1999-2005 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 076 - EARTHACTION - INTERNET FORUM TO SOLVE GLOBAL PROBLEMS, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 077 - GLOBAL EXCHANGE - TO PROMOTE THE MOVIE "LIFE AND DEBT", 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 078 - ANDES ASSOCIATION (PERU) - IPR IN THE ANDES, 2001-2004 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 082 - PESTICIDE ACTION NETWORK AFRICA (SENEGAL) - BIOTECHNOLOGY AND BIOLOGICAL SECURITY IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 083 - AMAZON CONSERVATION TEAM - SEMINAR ON HUMAN HEALTH AND BIODIVERSITY, 2001-2002 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 086 - LAWYERS COMMITTEE FOR HUMAN RIGHTS - PROMOTING WORKER'S RIGHTS IN THE GLOBAL ECONOMY, 2001-2003 (Box R3822)
    - 2001 GI 087 - UNITED NATIONS UNIVERSITY (JAPAN) - WORKSHOP ON CAPACITY DEVELOPMENT FOR THE BIOSAFETY OF GMOs IN SOUTHEAST ASIA, 2001-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 089 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL ON HUMAN RIGHTS POLICY (SWITZERLAND) - MEETING ON HUMAN RIGHTS AND MILITARY INTERVENTION, 2000-2005 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 091 - COMMUNITY TECHNOLOGY DEVELOPMENT TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - WORKSHOP ON BIOSAFETY PROTOCOL, 2001-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 093 - LA MUJER OBRERA - CONFERENCE "WOMEN AND WORK", 2001-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 094 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - CAPACITY OF PUBLIC POLICY AND BENEFICIAL SOCIETAL OUTCOMES, 2001-2004 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 096 - DEVELOPMENT GROUP FOR ALTERNATIVE POLICIES - SAPRIN NETWORK, 2000-2004 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 098 - OPENDEMOCRACY (ENGLAND) - NETWORK ON GLOBAL ISSUES, 2001-2004 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 099 - FOUNDATION GLOBAL ETHIC (GERMANY) - EXHIBITION ON WORLD RELIGION, PEACE AND ETHICS IN NEW YORK, 2001-2002 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 101 - TIDES CENTER - WOMEN AT WORK IN THE DEVELOPING WORLD, 2000-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 105 - WORKER RIGHTS CONSORTIUM - MONITORING LABOR CONDITIONS, 2001-2002 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 106 - UNIVERSITY OF VICTORIA (CANADA) - GLOBAL KNOWLEDGE AND DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, 2001-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 109 - INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURE AND TRADE POLICY - TRADE INFORMATION PROJECTS AND TRIPs ACTION NETWORK, 2001-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 GI 111 - CENTER FOR ECONOMIC AND POLICY RESEARCH - ECONOMIC INTEGRATION AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, 2000-2003 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 Gl 112 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - HUMAN RIGHTS PROGRAM, 2001-2004 (Box R3823)
    - 2001 Gl 115 - THIRD WORLD NETWORK (GHANA) - AFRICA TRADE NETWORK, 2001-2004 (Box R3823)
    - 2002 GI 001 - ALLIANCE OF SMALL ISLAND STATES - WORKSHOP ON TRADE AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT IN JAMAICA, 2001-2002 (Box R3823)
    - 2002 GI 013 - WORLD BANK - INTERNATIONAL COMPARISON PROGRAM MEETING (Box R3823)
    - 2002 GI 017 - QUEEN MARY, UNIVERSITY OF LONDON (ENGLAND) - IPR POLICY CAPACITY IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2002-2004 (Box R3824)
    - 2002 GI 035 - UNITED NATIONS ASSOCIATION OF THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA - MEETING AS PART OF THE PARTNERSHIP ON PEACE-BUILDING AND RULE OF LAW, 2002-2004 (Box R3824)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2006.114.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 GP 010 - OAXACA COMMUNITY FOUNDATION (MEXICO) - GENERAL SUPPORT, 2000-2003 (Box R3824)
    - 2000 GP 011 - GIVE2ASIA - PHILANTHROPY FOR ASIA, 2000-2006 (Box R3824)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2006.114.3; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 HE 002 - ACTION ON SMOKING AND HEALTH FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - SOUTHEAST ASIA TOBACCO CONTROL WORKSHOP, 1999-2006 (Box R3824)
    - 2000 HE 006 - INDONESIA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - WORKSHOP WTO/TRIPS AGREEMENT AND ACCESS TO DRUGS, 2000-2003 (Box R3824)
    - 2000 HE 009 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - SEMINARS ON COMMUNICATIONS TECHNOLOGIES AND HEALTH IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 2000-2002 (Box R3824)
    - 2000 HE 014 - COMMONWEALTH REGIONAL HEALTH COMMUNITY SECRETARIAT FOR EAST, CENTRAL, AND SOUTHERN AFRICA - MINISTERIAL AIDS MEETING, 2000-2003 (Box R3824)
    - 2000 HE 022 - MINISTRY OF HEALTH (GHANA) - NAVRONGO COMMUNITY HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING PROJECT, 1992-2003; 2 folders. (Box R3824)
    - 2000 HE 022 - MINISTRY OF HEALTH (GHANA) - NAVRONGO COMMUNITY HEALTH AND FAMILY PLANNING PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1992-2003; 4 folders. (Box R3824, Box R3825)
    - 2000 HE 025 - UNIVERSITY OF MANITOBA (CANADA) - REGULAR ROUTINE CHEMOPROPHYLAXIS TO REDUCE SEXUALLY TRANSMITTED DISEASES AMONG WOMEN SEX WORKERS IN KENYA, 1996-2003 (Box R3825)
    - 2000 HE 052 - UGANDA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - DISEASE SURVEILLANCE NETWORK, 2000-2003 (Box R3825)
    - 2001 HE 015 - POPULATION COUNCIL - MICROBICIDES PUBLIC/PRIVATE INITIATIVE, 2001-2002 (Box R3825)
    - 2001 HE 016 - INTERNATIONAL UNION AGAINS TUBERCULOSIS AND LUNG DISEASE (FRANCE) - TRANSLATION OF TB MANUAL INTO ENGLISH, 2001-2004 (Box R3825)